# Michael Eduard Guivencan

Caloocan City North, National Capital Region, Philippines

meguivencan@gmail.com



+639287580119



linkedin.com/in/meguivencan



https://meguivencan.github.io/

# Summary

Experienced Web Development and Information Technology Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the telecommunication and food production industry. Skilled in ASP.NET C# MVC, JavaScript, Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET), HTML5, CSS, Git/Github, SQL(MSSQL, PosgreSQL, MySQL), Nginx, and IT Hardware Support. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Information System from University of Caloocan City.

# **Experience**



# **E-Sports Trader**

#### UNIONSPARK LTD

Oct 2019 - Present (1 year +)

- Monitor and manage odds and content for matches available in Sportsbook
- · Monitor and handle bets of fraudulent nature, monitor customers and analyse their behaviour and take appropriate actions based on profit/loss and other patterns
- Monitor and micro manage events with difficult positions and suspicious activity
- Propose betting fixtures and improvements
- Testing of front-end facing product on operators end and report issues

# Database Engineer/Programmer

#### Ericsson

Mar 2018 - Sep 2019 (1 year 7 months)

- Design the application to meet the business process design and application requirements (Web Application: ASP.NET Core C# MVC, Postgresql)
- Assist in defining and reviewing requirements and use cases for the application
- Configure, build, and test the application or technical architecture components
- Setting up and monitoring database of server (Linux Ubuntu with Nginx set up) for the site database.



# College Instructor

University of Caloocan City

Jan 2018 - Mar 2018 (3 months)

- Teach courses in their subject area(Computer Subjects)
- Work with students who are taking classes to improve their knowledge or career skills
- Develop an instructional plan (known as a course outline or syllabus) for the course(s) they teach and ensure that it meets college and department standards
- Plan lessons and assignments



#### IT Staff

Doxo Ingredients Inc.

Jun 2016 - Dec 2017 (1 year 7 months)

• Install and configure computer hardware operating systems and applications

- Monitor and maintain computer systems and networks
- Talk staff or clients through a series of actions, either face-to-face or over the phone, to help set up systems or resolve issues
- Troubleshoot system and network problems, diagnosing and solving hardware or software faults
- Replace parts as required

# **Education**



# University of Caloocan City

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information System 2012 - 2016

### Skills

IT Hardware Support • C# • Visual Basic .NET (VB.NET) • Information Technology • ASP.NET Core • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • SQL • GitHub • JavaScript